Contact

+91 9490 724 987 (Mobile) merajkhanselenium@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/meraj-khan-121352114 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Selenium

Appium

Certifications

Scrum Fundamentals Certified

Meraj Khan

Automation Engineer at ValueLabs

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Experienced Software Quality Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Process & Project Management, Customer Service, and Requirements Analysis with Communication. Strong quality assurance professional with a Bachelor's in Computer Application focused in Computer Software Engineering from PNC & Vijay Institute of Engineering & Technology.

Experience

ValueLabs Sr. Test Engineer October 2018 - Present Hyderabad Area, India

Logic Systems
Test Automation Engineer
March 2018 - October 2018 (8 months)
Jeddah Governorate, Saudi Arabia

http://www.logicsystems-me.com

Provide enterprise automation solutions across the entire organization using a fully integrated solution. Our team of Experts helps guide you to implement the best application processes that suite your business

Xtream IT People Software Development Engineer In Test February 2016 - February 2018 (2 years 1 month) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

https://www.xtreamit.com

Xtream IT's expertise in the Direct and Indirect Tax Domain has spanned more than a decade. Over that time, we've continued to focus on and make use of

cutting-edge technology and software best practices to develop innovative yet user-friendly solutions.

XIT Solutions Inc.
Software Development Engineer In Test
February 2016 - February 2018 (2 years 1 month)
Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Acharya Nagarjuna University

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Programming, Specific Applications · (2016 - 2019)

PNC & Vijai Institute of Engineering & Technology Bachelor's in Computer Application, Computer Software Engineering · (2012 - 2015)